Guide to the Jack Burke Jr. papers/Champions Golf Club records; 1956-2017 MS 525
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Cup Matches, 1966 - 2006
  - Cup matches information sent to members, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cup matches reservations, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Cup matches letter of invitation, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Cup matches - requested invitations but did not get to play, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Cup matches invitations turned down, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Cup matches sponsors, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Cup matches check list, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Cup matches, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Cup matches qualifications, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Cup matches invitations, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Cup matches invitations turned down, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Cup matches thank you letters, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Cup matches sponsors, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Cup matches, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Cup matches, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Cup matches pairings, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Cup matches invitations, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Cup matches invitation correspondence, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Cup matches invitations turned down, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Cup matches thank you letters, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Cup matches financal and promotional, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Cup matches invitations, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Cup matches thank you letters, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Cup matches, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cup matches, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Cup matches, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cup matches, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Cup matches, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Cup matches sponsors, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Cup matches sponsors, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Cup matches publicity, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cup matches Report to the U. S. G. A., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Cup matches publicity, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Cup matches sponsors, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Cup matches financial, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Cup matches, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Champions cup original lists and forms, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Cup matches sponsors, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Cup matches publicity, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Cup matches sponsors, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Cup matches, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Cup matches financial, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Cup matches publicity, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Cup matches qualifier, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Cup matches thank you letters, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Cup matches publicity, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Cup matches financial, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Champions cup qualifier, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Cup matches publicity, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Cup qualifier, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Cup matches financial, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Cup matches publicity, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Cup matches photographs, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Cup matches financial, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Cup matches photographs, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Cup matches, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Cup matches original lists and forms, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Cup matches thank you letters, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Cup matches financial, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Cup matches photographs, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Cup matches, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Cup matches thank you letters, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Cup matches financial, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Cup matches, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Cup matches thank you letters, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Cup matches, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Cup matches lists, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Cup matches financial, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Cup matches thank you letters, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Cup matches, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Cup matches financial, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Cup matches thank you letters, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Cup matches lists and forms, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Cup matches, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Cup matches financial, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Cup matches lists, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Cup matches forms and club correspondence, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cup matches, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Champions Cup Invitational/Part 1, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Champions Cup Invitational/Part 2, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Cup matches caddie and cart information, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - U. S. Amateur Championship sponsors, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - U. S. Amateur Championship marshalls, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Houston Open marshall information, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Kite vs. Crenshaw match, September 2, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - TGA Texas Mid Amateur Championship, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - International Association of Golf Administrators Conference, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Series VI: Champions Golf Club property records, 1968 - 2006
  - Warranty Deeds, Billy Alexander, 1990 - 1993 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Evans - Monical, Inc. Interior Consultants, 1968 -1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Clubhouse construction, 1983 - 1990 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Northgate Mobile Homes, Inc., 1979 - 1995 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Property at NW corner of FM 1960 at Champions Dr., 1999 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Club artwork, 1982 - 2006 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Marilyn M. Hillory artwork for cards, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Bob Pringle and Ken Reed, 2002 - 2006 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Taft Broadcasting, 1999 - 2000 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - "Tomorrow's Champion" oil painting - Buck Wynne Wolley, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Scorecard and logo renovation, 2001 - 2003 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Series VII: Member-Guest Tournaments, 1966 - 2004
  - Member - Guest Tournament correspondence, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Member - Guest Tournament finances, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Member - Guest Tournament, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Member newsletters, 1983 -2002 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Transmittals to William H. Shoemaker Co., 2000 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Reports to the membership, 1998 - 2001 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Series VIII: PGA Tour records, 1997 - 2006
  - Tour Championship websites, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Tour Championship scrip books, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Tour Championship employee ticket orders, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Tour Championship invoices, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Inside the Tour Championship newsletters, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Tour Championship maps, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Tour Championship sales and inventory, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Tour Championship order forms, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Tour Championship volunteers, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Tour Championship schedules, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Tour Championship memos, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Tour Championship programs and brochures, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Tour Championship security, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Tour Championship menus, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - British and American Ryder Cup teams, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - PGA Tour Championship, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - PGA Tour Championship/Part 1, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - PGA Tour Championship/Part 2, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - PGA Tour Championship/Part 1, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - PGA Tour Championship/Part 2, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - PGA Tour Championship/Part 1, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - PGA Tour Championship/Part 2, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - PGA Tour Championship/Part 1, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - PGA Tour Championship/Part 2, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - PGA Tour Championship contracts, 2000 - 2006 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Series IX: Board of Directors records, 1957 - 2007
  - Board of Directors ballots, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors ballots, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors ballots, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors ballots, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors ballots, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors ballots, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors ballots, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Declaration of Trust, Trustees' Authorization, Stock Subcription Agreement, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors minutes: Special meeting, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Champions Golf Club, Inc. Articles of Incorporation, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors, 1965 - 1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors notices of meetings and minutes, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors items pending, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors meeting notes, March 21, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors agenda and relative materials, June 28, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors agenda and relative information, August 8, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors minutes, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Annual shareholders meeting, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Annual shareholders meeting, 1960 - 2007 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Champions Golf Club, Inc. stockholders, 1990 - 1991 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Alpha member list, April 11, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Series X: Legal and business records, 1972 - 2006
  - Golf course legal issues, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Legal correspondence, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Chamberlain Hrdlicka Attorneys at Law, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Johanson Fairless, L.L. P. lawyers, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers lawsuit/Part 1, 1987 - 1990 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers lawsuit/Part 2, 1987 - 1990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Champions Golf Club, Inc. trademark lawsuit/Part 1, 1989 - 1994 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Champions Golf Club, Inc. trademark lawsuit/Part 2, 1989 - 1994 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Champions Golf Club, Inc. trademark lawsuit/Part 3, 1989 - 1994 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Champions Golf Club, Inc. trademark lawsuit/Part 4, 1989 - 1994 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Champions Golf Club, Inc. trademark lawsuit/Part 1, 1989 - 1996 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Champions Golf Club, Inc. trademark lawsuit/art 2, 1989 - 1996 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Champions Golf Club, Inc. trademark lawsuit/Part 3, 1989 - 1996 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Champions Club, Omaha, Nebraska lawsuit, 2000 - 2003 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Economy Gas, Inc. and Joe D. Havens lawsuit/Part 1, 1993 - 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Economy Gas, Inc. and Joe D. Havens lawsuit/Part 2, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Darryl Fawcett lawsuit, 1992 - 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Sarah and Robert Milam lawsuit, 1990 - 1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Marbella Rivera charge of discrimination, 1998 - 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Nabisco Championships contracts, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Event invoices, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Event invoices, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Event invoices, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - PGA Golf professional compensation survey summary, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Summary of 401k plan description, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - IRS examination - R. S. Kreiger, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Charitable contributions/Part 1, 1998 - 2007 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Charitable contributions/Part 2, 1998 - 2007 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Rice University scholarship donation, 2002 - 2004 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Earl Elliott Memorial Rice University Scholarship Fund Tournament, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Yound Audiences of Houston, Inc., 2002 - 2004 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Kimberley Martin - Shriner's Hospital for Crippled Children, 1976 -1990s (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - William H. Shoemaker Co. auditor's reports, 1973 - 1981 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - William H. Shoemaker Co. auditor's reports, 1982 - 1986 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - The Community Foundation of Western North Carolina, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Texas State Securities Board, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Phone and Address Books, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Phone Messages, March 2001-April 2002 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Phone Messages, April-June 2002 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Phone Messages, June-September 2002 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Phone Messages, September-November 2002 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Phone Messages, November 2002-February 2003 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Series XI: Publications, 1961 - 2006
  - Jack Burke Jr. memoir notes, 1998 - 1999 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Jack Burke Jr. roast notes, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Jack Burke Jr. correspondence, 2004 - 2006 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Champions Golf Club Book second edition, 2001 - 2002 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Deand McNally Executive Golfer's Guide, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Golf Digest, "Living Legends Turn Back the Clock", May 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Gold Digest, "Nobody's Fool", July 2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - GolfWeek, "Americas's Best Classical Courses", March 19, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - GolfWeek, "Fall Guy", November 10, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Golf World, obituary, June 15, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Golf World, "Practice Makes Perfect", September 3, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1961 - 1965 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Houston Champions International photographs newsclippings, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Golf newspaper clippings, 1980 -1989 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Golf newspaper clippings, 1990 - 1999 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Golf newspaper clippings, 2000 - 2009 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Golf newspaper clippings, 2010 - 2019 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Houston Post, "Top 20 Houston Area Golf Courses", December 25, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - "Champions Golf Club opens to African - Americans", 1990 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Gulf Coast Golfer, Volume 7 No 2, Jimmy Burke obituary, July 1990 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Nabisco Championships, October 1990 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Dallas Morning News, "Texas Golf 1996" (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Houston Chronicle, "Texas Golf 2001 Guide to States's Best Courses" (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Tour Championship, November 2001 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - 2003 Tour Championship, November 2003 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Dallas Morning News, "Texas Golf 2004" (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Press releases, 2000 - 2004 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Undated photographs (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - James Demaret flight log pilot license, 1974 - 1981 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Mary Brown retirement memorabilia (with autographs), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Champions Golf Club membership directory, 1957-1997 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Champions Golf Club membership prospectus (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Champions Golf Club mission statement (revised), 2001 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - U.S. Golf Association oral history collection: Jack Burke [transcript], 1993-11-18 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Series XII: Video, 1967 - 2005
  - Donnie Blanz Live Demo (Box 24)
  - The Ryder Cup, 1967 (Box 24)
  - The Ryder Cup, 1967 (First 13 Minutes Copy) (Box 24)
  - Orville Moody at Champions (US Open), 1969 (Box 24)
  - The Ryder Cup (1967) and Orville Moody at Champions (1969) - 2 DVD's (Box 24)
  - US Open, 1969 (Box 24)
  - The Legends of Golf, 1980 (Box 24)
  - Champions Golf Club, 12/22/87 (Box 24)
  - Nabisco Championship, 1990 (First 12 Minutes Copy) (Box 24)
  - Deposition of Jack Valenti Re: Champions Golf Club, 2/23/1994 (Box 24)
  - "A Tour of Champions Golf Club with Jackie Burke", 4/94 (Box 24)
  - Shell's Wonderful World of Golf, Crenshaw vs. Kite, Champions Golf Club, 11/12/96 (Box 24)
  - Jack Burke Jr. Roast, February 29, 2000 (Box 24)
    Scope and Contents
    These born digital video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy mp4.
  - "Beeming with Pride" The Official Highlight Video of the 2002 PGA Championship (Box 24)
  - World Golf Hall of Fame Induction Ceremony, 2003 (Box 24)
  - Watson/Stewart Award, 11/3/03 (Box 24)
  - 2003 Tour Championship Dinner Video (Box 24)
  - Tour Championship "Home of Champions", 11/2/03 (Box 24)
  - Tour Championship "The Fall Finish", 11/6/03 (Box 24)
  - Tour Championship "The Fall Finish", 11/7/03 (Box 24)
  - Tour Championship "The Fall Finish", 11/8/03 (Box 24)
  - Tour Championship "The Fall Finish - Noon", 11/9/03 (Box 24)
  - Tour Championship "The Fall Finish - 11PM", 11/9/03 (Box 24)
  - The Opening Ceremony for Super Bowl XXXVIII, January 26, 2004 (Box 24)
  - 2004 Bob Jones Award Video, Jack Burke Jr. (Box 24)
  - 2004 Bob Jones Award Video (2 DVD's), Jack Burke Jr. (Box 24)
  - 2004 Bob Jones Award Dinner Video, 2/7/04 (Box 24)
  - Lifetime Achievement Award, Jack Burke Jr. (Box 24)
  - Champions Golf Club Member-Guest Invitation, 2005 (Box 24)
  - "40 Years of Champions", KTRK TV (Box 24)
  - "The Spirit of the Game" An Etiquette Program from the United States Golf Association (Box 24)
- Series XIII: Memorabilia
  - Curtis Cup signed flag with accompanying letters/cards, 2016 (Box 25)
  - Golf ball marker (from 60th anniversary), 2017 (Box 25)
  - Golf bag tag (from 60th anniversary), 2017 (Box 25)